# DEVANSH SRIVASTAVA

Graphic Designer | UI/UX Designer

### **Portfolio**

https://groovydesignstudio.github.io

#### Contact

#### E-mail

srivastava002dev@gmail.com

#### Phone

8077599341, 8445609245

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/devansh-srivastava-08

#### **Address**

Uttrakhand, 244713

# **Key Skills**

Graphic Design

UI/UX Design

Visual Design

Web Design

**Vector Illustration** 

Digital Marketing

#### Software

Figma

Adobe Xd

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Dimentions

Adobe Indesign

Canva

Creative years experienced of Graphic and UI/UX Designs adept in creating powerful visual designs using digital illustration, images and typography. committed to helping clients shape their brand identity through the use of compelling graphics. Accustomed to collaborating with other creative professionals to achieve project goals.

## **Work History**

Febaury 2022-Currently working

### **ToggIr Solutions Private limited**

Graphic Designer, Ui Designer & Digital Marketing

- Made daily design post for social media, making monthly budget for all social media platform
- Posting every day post on social media
- Used photoshop and illustrator to make everyday posts
- Tacking every day campaign report and sending to sales department
- Marketing campaigns to support key business initiatives a new business development and customer experience.
- Analyzed and reported social media and online marketing campaign results.
- Increased customer engagement through social media.
- Created social media content with consistent content and tone.
- Successfully launched online consumer targeting and marketing strategy

May 2021-August 2021

### Fliqaindia

Graphic Designer & UI Designer

- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Designed website layouts, templates and unique branded looks.
- Worked with Software and Type of design systems to develop and present prototypes for focus group evaluation.
- Applied creative expertise to present marketing concepts.
- Created broad range of work using various design techniques.
- Created designs and collaborated with technical team to complete projects.
- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection.
- Used photoshop to develop product mockups and prototype designs.

January 2021-March 2021

#### **Helpholics**

Graphic Designer

- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Designed creative digital displays used in on-line advertising for local businesses.
- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection.
- Put together videos for social media, advertising and informational purposes.
- Capitalized on talents in field to support promotions with many designs.
- Completed key different design projects for clients.

# DEVANSH SRIVASTAVA

Graphic Designer | UI/UX Designer

#### **Interests**

Football

Badminton

Athletics

Making designs

## Language

Hindi

English

Spanish (Beginner)

July 2020-September 2020

### **Sportsthat**

Graphic Designer

- Promoted company's events by designing marketing materials such as posters, digital invites and brochures.
- Prepared images to coincide with social and blog posts.
- Used Photoshop and Illustrator to create images and layouts for multiple projects.
- Capitalized on talents in field to support promotions with many designs.

November 2019-January 2020

## Carpathy

Graphic Designer

- Worked closely with Carpathy to maintain optimum levels of communication to effectively and efficiently complete projects.
- Applied knowledge of production to create high-quality images.
- Developed creative design for marketing packages, including print materials, brochures, banners and signs.
- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection.
- Created plans and communicated deadlines to ensure projects were completed on time.

June 2019-August 2019

#### **Talentedge**

Graphic Designer

- Conducted research, gathered information from multiple sources and presented results.
- Developed Application UIs via emerging Front End Technologies
- Created maps, models and templates for diverse projects.
- · Created design work for digital campaigns.
- Prepared images to coincide with social and blog posts.
- Completed key design projects for company.

## **Education**

August 2017-August 2020

### Bachelor of Design: Graphic Design

Apeejay Stya University - Haryana

References: Available on request